环陆桥连接申请…来自苏格兰
Incoming groundbridge request... from Scotland.
千斤顶 出什么事了？
Wheeljack, what happened?
其他人在哪儿？
Where are the others?
在通天晓的飞船里享受长途旅行呢 我敢肯定
Having a swell time taking the long way home in Ultra Magnus' boat, I'm sure.
包括神子在内
Miko included.
难怪她买瓶汽水需要这么久
I wondered what was taking so long with those sodas.
你拿到巨狰狞的骸骨了吗？
Did you secure the Predacon bone?
这个…狩猎者们内讧了 大夫
The Beast Hunt kind of imploded, Doc.
我刚刚又收到了一条虎子活动的消息 就在新墨西哥洲的陶斯城外
Well, I just got wind of another 'Con hotspot. Right outside of Taos, New Mexico.
鉴于擎天柱的小分队还没从产油国回来…
Since Prime's unit isn't back from oil country...
拉夫 把环陆桥指向福勒探员提供的坐标
Raf, set a bridge for Fowler's coordinates.
你 跟我来
You, roll with me.
不去行不？
Not today, all right?
如果你放心我独自前往 那不去也罢
If you're all right sending me out there alone.
我就喜欢独来独往
Alone's how I prefer to roll.
千斤顶 你要让我放下手头的繁重工作 去外面冒险吗？
Wheeljack, you do not want to make me abandon a complex equation to venture outside my comfort zone.
呃 好吧
Huh... Fine...
但要事先声明一下
But in case you haven't figured it out...
跟别人合作不是我的菜
I don't play well with others.
该死！
Scrap.
知道我最喜欢车型杂兵们哪一点吗？
Know what I love most about Vehicon troopers?
他们很容易走神
They're easily distracted.
走你！
Ya!
哈！
Ha!
喝！
Huh!
你确定你不是救援队的？
You sure you weren't a Wrecker?
你确定合作不是你的菜？
You sure you don't play well with others?
打得漂亮 杰克！
Nice shooting, Tex.
嗨 妈妈 有事吗？
Hey, Mom, what's up?
达比护士
Nurse Darby
什么风把你给吹来了？
what brings you here?
你向我们慷慨捐赠的医药物资
The medical supplies you so graciously offered to donate
杰克总是忘记带回家
that Jack keeps forgetting to bring home.
医院十分感激你的慷慨相助 福勒探员
The hospital appreciates your generosity, Agent Fowler.
叫我威廉就行了
Please, call me William.
伙计们 我在一个博物馆里找到了巨狰狞的爪子
Guys, I found a Predacon talon... in a museum.
它1922年出土的时候让科学家们大伤脑筋 所以一直被收在仓库里
Scientists were totally stumped when they excavated it in 1922, so it's been in storage.
但我们的野兽猎人都被派出去了
But we're fresh out of Beast Hunters.
好吧…我选择急救车辆为变形模式 可不是白给的
Heh... I didn't choose "emergency" as my vehicle mode for laughs.
不一定非得汽车人出马嘛
Not sure you need a 'Bot.
或许你们应该等擎天柱回来
Maybe you should all just wait for Optimus.
请注意 达比护士
I'll have you known, nurse Darby.
在擎天柱出现前 我可是当了30年游骑兵和联邦特工的
I was an army Ranger and federal Agent for Unit-E three decades before I'd ever heard the name Optimus Prime.
这类零风险公务对我来说小菜一碟
I'm more than equipped to handle a milk run.
其实 你也可以一起来的
In fact, why don't you tag along?
哦 这不太好吧
Oh, I don't know about that.
哦 绝对不行
Oh, a... absolutely not.
妈妈 我可不想让你跟虎子有任何接触 这不…
Mom, I don't want you anywhere near anything 'Con. It's not...
安全？我未成年的儿子真的想告诉我\N他可以开心地跑去塞博特恩
Safe? Is my teenage son seriously going to tell me that its fine for him to travel all the way to Cybertron
而他的老妈却不能参加那个…那个…
but his mother can't be trusted to go on a... on a...
零风险公务
Milk run.
零风险公务？
A milk run?
不 我…我…你不是有乳糖不耐症吗？而我…
No, I... it's just... you're lactose intolerant, and I...
我们走 福勒探员
Come on, Agent Fowler.
啊 干得漂亮 我的爱宠
Ah, you performed well, my pet.
这将对巨狰狞队伍的壮大做出巨大的贡献
This will be a splendid contribution to the spawning of your Predacon brethren.
我的君王 我们找到了另一处\N震荡波的巨狰狞能量信号 微弱但很稳定
My liege, we've located another of Shockwave's Predacon energy signatures. Weak, but steady.
好极了！
Excellent.
击倒 不要空手回来见我
Knockout, do not return empty-handed.
我？我的字典里没有这个字
Me? Don't know the meaning of the word.
空手不是两个字吗？
Isn't "empty-handed" two words?
瞧你能耐的 找回丢失的装甲了吗？
You would know, or did your missing armor turn up?
你这只会在地上爬的…
Why, you wheel-bound...
红蜘蛛 你今天已经够让我失望的了
Starscream! You have failed me enough for one day.
回去继续搜索其他巨狰狞的能量信号 赶快！
Assume the task of monitoring for Predacon energy signatures, at once!
是 我的君王
Yes, my liege.
你肯定会像我一样发现这份\N工作能让你神清气爽 小红同学
I'm sure you'll find the gig as invigorating as I did, "Screamer".
啊…
Ah...
震荡波已经开始用目前采集到的标本进行克隆了
Shockwave has initiated the cloning process with the specimens gathered thus far.
这只巨狰狞 只不过是新一波超级野兽机器战士中的先锋而已
The Predacon currently among us will be but the first of a new wave of beast machine super-soldiers.
你在这里晃荡什么？
What are you lurking about for?
滚回你的狗窝去！
Get back to your kennel.
啊！
Ah!
呃！
Um!
啊！你这没脑子的畜牲 瞧你干得好事！
Ah! You mindless brute, look what you've done!
你很安静啊 千斤顶
You're awfully quiet, Wheeljack.
我向来不喜欢闲聊
I've never been one for chitchat.
你为什么要假装呢？
Why do you pretend?
如果你真想单干 今天早就闪人了 但是你没有
If you really wanted to roll alone, you would've hit the open road today. But you didn't.
你乘坐环陆桥返回了基地
You called for a 'bridge back to base.
嘿！别自作聪明了
Hey. Don't assume you know me.
我没有
I'm not assuming.
现在 可以聊聊到底发生了什么事吗？
Now, care to chitchat about what happened out there?
我怎么说来着 零风险公务
What did I tell you? Milk run.
是啊 就是那家伙的脾气有点古怪
With one cranky cow.
馆长？好像他看管的是蒙娜丽莎\N而不是从哈丁时期就被尘封的史前螺母似的
The curator? Acted like he was guarding the Mona Lisa, instead of some prehistoric lug nut that's been gathering dust since Harding was president.
我得说 福勒探员 你处理得当
I have to say, Agent Fowler, you handled him well.
我很钦佩
I was quite impressed.
达比护士 依我说你比我前妻要更为出色
Nurse Darby, I'd say that puts you one step ahead of my ex.
嗯 离婚了 是吧？
Hmm. Divorced, huh?
啊…是的 你呢？
Ah... Yeah. What about you?
和达比先生之间有什么故事？
What's the story with Mr. Darby?
嗯…说起来更像是个传奇故事
Ah... More like a saga
不过…你肯定听过类似的
but one I'm sure you've heard before.
我是来帮你们两个鸡蛋挑骨头的
I have a bone to pick with both of you.
快跑！
Run!
平静 放松 欣赏下风景吧！
Kick back, relax, and enjoy the scenery.
击倒呼叫威震天陛下！
Knockout to Lord Megatron.
古代巨狰狞的爪子已经到手 附赠两个汽车人的宠物
I have secured one vintage Predacon talon, plus two of the Autobots' pets
您拿去当人质也好 做实验也罢 总之随您的便
for you to employ as hostages, lab experiments, well anyway you see fit
所以赶紧地 老大 说您爱人家胜过红蜘蛛
so go on, Big M, tell me you love me more than Starscream.
君王？呃…我太放肆了？
My liege? Hello? Too familiar?
这只原始的杂种狗破坏了我们整个通讯网络
The primitive mutt demolishes our entire communications network
而威震天陛下还打算要繁殖更多的？
and lord Megatron intends to breed more of it?
你们俩能快点吗？\N要在我们的主人为这些小事伤脑筋之前修好它
Would you two hurry? I want this fixed before our Master is bothered by such distracting minutiae.
现在重置访问代码并重启…
Entering access override code and rebooting now.
啊！不 不不不不不不！
Ah! No! No, no, no, no...!
他们去了有好一阵了
It's really taking them a while.
阿尔茜和千斤顶？
Arcee and Wheeljack?
我妈妈和福勒探员
My Mom and Agent Fowler.
嗯 也许他们在途中共进晚餐呢
Hum... Maybe they stopped for dinner.
大人拍拖时不就是这样吗？
Isn't that what grown-ups do when they're dating?
大人们是因为饿才这么做！
It's what grown-ups do when they're hungry.
- 妈妈？\N- 再猜 兔小子杰克！
- Mom.\N- Guess again, Jack rabbit.
我希望你现在不渴了 因为我带回来的东西可比饮料酷多了！
and I hope you're not still thirsty because I'm bringing back something way cooler that sodas.
我现在不能聊天 神子 我在等电话
I can't talk, Miko. I need to leave this line free.
等下 先别挂 千斤顶回去了吗？
Wait, don't hang up. Did Wheeljack show?
我想隔板很担心他
I think Bulkhead's really worried about him.
千斤顶没事 他跟阿尔茜执行任务去了
Wheeljack is fine. He's on a mission with Arcee.
千斤顶已经有新搭档了？太无情了！
Wheeljack's riding with a new partner already? That's cold.
什么？不 就是一个任务而已 不是搭档关系
What? No. It's just one mission, they're not partners.
哈哈 我一直在猜这两位独行侠什么时候能来电
Haha. I wondered how long it would take our two lone wolves to hook up.
我都说了我们应该等擎天柱
I told you we should have waited for Optimus.
到底还是说了 “我不是跟你说过了吗”
There it is. The "I told you so."
反正 我不买账 这个虎子就守在博物馆那儿
Well, no sale, sister. The 'Con was at the museum.
如果我们等的话 在擎天柱到达之前他就把爪子抢到手了
If we had waited, he would have snagged the talon before Prime got there.
就我们现在所处的局面 那又有什么不同？
And given our current situation, what difference would that have made?
喂！你们两个拍拖有多久了？\N这吵起架来就跟老夫老妻似的
Hello? How long have you two been dating? Because you bicker like an old married couple.
什么？
What?
我们没拍拖
We're not dating.
说老实话 我觉得那很恶心唉！
Frankly, I find it repulsive
你们这些肉虫…结合的整个概念都…妈呀哎
the whole idea of you fleshies... interfacing...[shivers]
击倒呼叫基地 再次请求 接我回家！
Knockout to base, requesting pick up, again...
好吧 到底有没有人在听啊？
All right, is anyone up there receiving me?!
达比护士 琼
Nurse Darby. June.
如果这个虎子把我们带到威震天的老窝 汽车人找到我们的机率
If this 'Con gets us to Megatron's warship, the chances of the 'bots ever finding us
恐怕连千分之一都不到
decrease a thousand fold.
永远不要让霸天虎把你带到别处去
Never let a Decepticon take you to a second location.
在博物馆那儿我被缴了械 你有没有可以当作武器的东西？
He disarmed me back at the museum. Do you have anything we could use as a weapon?
胡椒粉喷雾剂？
Pepper spray?
喷虎子？
On a 'Bot?
像通天晓那样的家伙
Guys like 'Magnus...
烦不到我头上 只有我烦他们的份儿
I don't let them peel my paint. I peel theirs.
所以让你恼火的不是新指挥官 而是隔板
So if it isn't the new Commander who's grinding your gears, it's Bulkhead.
呃…看到一个雷霆救援队员变得畏首畏尾 很是让人恼火
Hum... Just burns me up when a Wrecker goes soft.
听着 千斤顶 在你心中雷霆救援队永远都是老样子
Look, Wheeljack. You'll always have the Wreckers as you knew them, in here.
时代在变化
Times change
铁打的营盘流水的兵 如果你不能适应 便无法生存
players come and go, and if you can't adapt, you'll rust
就像我们正在挖的骨头一样
like the bones we're digging for.
别跟隔板疏远了 如果他出了事 你永远都不会原谅自己的
Don't push Bulkhead away. If something happened to him, you'd never forgive yourself.
相信我 我深有体会
Trust me, I know.
击倒呼叫基地 请求环陆桥 第N次呼叫了
Knockout to base, requesting groundbridge for the umpteenth time.
基地 请回复
Come in, base.
啊 人家不能开一夜的车…
Ohh. I can't drive around all night...
…怎么？
- what?\N- Oh!
注意轮圈！
Watch the rims!
趁现在！
Now!
很好 这可真是太帅了！
Well, isn't that just grand?
啊…上帝啊…
Ah! God do...
我说“帅”了吗？人家是说这可真是太无礼了！
Did I say "grand"? I meant totally rude.
啊！我的光学镜！
Ahh! My optics!
哦 现在我们要玩人类的游戏吗？
Oh! Are we playing a human game now?
因为我很愿意教你霸天虎的玩法――捉迷杀 哈哈哈！
Because I would be happy to teach you the Decepticon version: "hide-and-go-shriek". Ha ha ha!
琼…琼…你在哪儿？
June! June, where are you?
啊哈！
Aha!
好了 小女人 出来吧
All right, little lady, show yourself.
不然我就把这个潮男变成柏油路上的一滩血水！
Or I turn the snappy dresser here into a sloppy stain on the tarmac.
你已拨通了福勒探员 听到星条旗的哔哔声请留言
You've reached special Agent William Fowler. Leave a message at the star-spangled beep.
直接跑到留言了 就像妈妈的手机一样
Straight to voicemail, just like Mom's cell.
也许他们去看电影了
Maybe they went to a movie?
啊 好吧 逃避小隔
Hum... Okay. Running from Bulk
拒绝通话 我真是个懦夫
shutting down like that, pretty spineless of me.
往好处想 现在你骨头硬多了
On the bright side, you have plenty of backbone now.
阿尔茜 我需要你帮忙
Arcee, I need your help.
我妈妈和福勒可能有大麻烦了
My Mom and Fowler may be in serious trouble.
最后的机会 女人类
Last chance, she-human.
如果你不拿着我的战利品在2.3秒内出现的话 你的男朋友…
If you're not out here with my prize in 2.3 seconds, your boyfriend here...
好 首先 他不是我男朋友
Okay, first, not my boyfriend.
啊…
Ah!
其次 你一根手指头也不能碰他
And second, you're not laying a metal digit on him.
要是你还想见到你宝贝爪子的话
Not if you ever want to see your precious talon again.
- 它在哪儿？\N- 放开她！
- Where is it?\N- Leave her alone!
我把它藏在一截车厢里了\N如果你放我们走 我就告诉你是哪一节
I hid it on a train car. Let us go, and I'll tell you which one.
班门弄斧 在欺诈的鼻祖面前
Try as you might, you can't con a 'Con.
系好安全带 前面的路会异常颠簸
Fasten your seatbelts. It's going to be a bumpy ride.
哦 对了 你们没法不系紧 我的错
Oh, wait, you can't unfasten your belts. My bad.
通讯中断有多久了？
Communications have been down for how long?!
声波就要把接收器修好了 主人
Soundwave practically has the dish repaired, Master.
对声波来说 这自然不在话下 而你…
Which is all well and good for Soundwave, but for you...
击倒呼叫威震天陛下 请回话！
Knockout to Lord Megatron, please, come in.
看？完全修好了
See? All fixed.
击倒 巨狰狞的骸骨到手没有？
Knockout, do you have the Predacon bone?
在我视野之内 君王 就像在后面追赶我的两个汽车人一样
In my sites, my liege. As are a pair of Autobots riding my rear.
知道了 务必把标本弄到手
Understood. Just make sure you secure the specimen.
好 一个诡诈的小人类会把骨头藏在哪一节车厢里呢？
Now, in which train car would a Deceptive little human choose to bury a bone?
我赌它在敞篷的那节车里
My money's on the convertible.
去救福勒和琼！
Get Fowler and June!
你们该下车了！
Here's where you get out.
威震天陛下 要是还不快开环陆桥 你的标本就要归汽车人了！
Lord Megatron, if a groundbridge doesn't open "tout de suite", your specimen will belong to the Autobots.
该死！
Scrap.
他们在哪儿？
Where are they?
在后面
In back.
- 啊!\N- 呼!
- Ah.\N- Whoo.
妈妈！
Mom!
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
无风险公务变成了高风险任务 但我和比尔都没事
The milk run turned a little sour, but Bill and I are just fine.
来 琼 坐下
Come on, June, sit down.
比尔？
Bill?
看来你的位置被“顶”了 杰克
Looks like you've been jacked, Jack
被千斤顶
by another 'Jack.
兄弟情胜过浪漫情啊！
Bro-mance trumps romance.
真高兴做你的兄弟 兄弟
Glad to be your bro, bro.
你今天干得很出色 击倒
You have served me well today, Knockout.
比某个人强出不少
which is more than I can say for some.
是那只畜牲扰乱通讯的 我的君王
It was the beast that disrupted communications, my liege.
我请求您重新考虑巨狰狞计划
I beg you to reconsider project Predacon.
那东西不可救药
The creature is incorrigible
除了最基本的智能外 一无是处
and void of all but the most rudimentary intelligence.